veria.com 2009-11-03

# Privacy Policy - Veria.com

Natural Wellness Corporation Ltd. ("Natural Wellness") is committed to protecting your privacy. We strongly believe in protecting the privacy of the personally identifiable information you share with us. We also believe it is important to inform you about how we will use your personal data and to give you choices about how those data will be used. Therefore, we encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully.

This Natural Wellness Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") explains data collection and use practices of the web property "www.veria.com" (the "Natural Wellness Website"). By accessing and using the Natural Wellness Website, you consent to the information collection and use practices described in the Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is subject to all the terms and conditions set forth in the Terms of Use for this Natural Wellness Website that is posted on the bottom of this page.

If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy, you may contact Natural Wellness using the information below (the "Contact Information"):

Email: [info@veria.com](mailto:info@veria.com)

Write to us at: Natural Wellness, Inc. 701 Highlander Blvd. #200, Arlington, TX 76015

If the Privacy Policy changes, we will post an updated version on the Natural Wellness Website. The policy revision date will be posted at the bottom of this page.

**Why should you share your personal data with Natural Wellness?**

Sharing your personally identifiable information enables us to offer you a number of benefits. It will make it easier and more convenient for you to:

o   Buy Natural Wellness products online;

o   Register your purchase so you can receive all the benefits to which your purchase entitles you;

o   Request information specific to your interests;

o   Participate in online communities;

o   Receive personalized messages and special offers that are relevant to your interests; and

o   Save time by storing your preferences.

You may choose to share your information with us in a number of ways online, such as completing a registration form to participate in our activities, ordering a product, entering a contest, registering a purchase, participating in a promotion, or subscribing to a newsletter. The information, as gathered, also will allow us to conduct market research to help develop better products, to provide more responsive customer service, and to improve our website.

Sometimes, Natural Wellness obtains your personal data from third parties. This collection of your personal data could occur if we buy a business of which you already are a customer or if you disclose your personal data to one of our partner companies. If you do not want us to use personal data which you have not directly provided to us, you can let us know by contacting us at the address listed above.

> ·         What kind of information does Natural Wellness collect about me?

> ·         How do you use my information?

> ·         Does Natural Wellness share my information with third parties?

> ·         How do I access my information? How do I change my information?

> ·         How does Natural Wellness protect kids' privacy?

> ·         What are cookies? How does Natural Wellness use cookies on its site?

> ·         How do I know if my subscription information is secure?

> ·         What about links to other Websites and services?

> ·         Can Natural Wellness change this privacy policy?

**What kind of information does Natural Wellness collect about me?**

We collect information you voluntarily submit to Natural Wellness, for example:

o   Identifying information, such as your name and email address

o   Security information, such as your username, password or password hint, and acceptance of policies, licenses and warranties

o   Contact information, such as your name, mailing address and phone number

o   Billing information, such as credit card, expiration date, billing address and account history

o   Natural Wellness Website behavior, such as the pages visited, downloads, or searches requested

o   Browser information such as the browser version, IP address, and the presence of various plug-ins and tools

**Top**

**How do you use my information?**

As appropriate, the personal information collected on the Natural Wellness Website will be used to operate or improve the Natural Wellness Website, to provide our many service(s), or to carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized. In support of these uses, Natural Wellness may use your personal information (i) to provide you with more effective customer service, (ii) to improve the Natural Wellness Website and any related Natural Wellness products or services, and (iii) to make the Natural Wellness Website easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information or by customizing the Natural Wellness Website to your particular preference or interests.

**Top**

**Does Natural Wellness share my information with third parties?**

Natural Wellness employs third party vendors and service providers ("Service Providers") to perform various functions on its behalf. Services provided by Service Providers may include, but are not limited to, (i) managing customer information, (ii) processing credit card or check card payments, (iii) analyzing data, (iv) developing, hosting and maintaining the Natural Wellness Website and any related databases, or (v) communicating with our customers about Natural Wellness. Natural Wellness does not authorize any of the Service Providers to make any other use of your information or to contact you outside the context of the services related to the Natural Wellness Website.

In the unlikely event of a sale of some or all of our business, Natural Wellness will disclose your personal information to a purchaser that agrees to abide by the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy.

Natural Wellness reserves the right to disclose information about you as required by law, in response to legal process and law enforcement requests, and as necessary to protect the property, interests and rights of Natural Wellness, its affiliates, and others.

**Top**

**How do I access my information? How do I change my information?**

Your personal information can be accessed and changed by contacting Natural Wellness using the Contact Information provided above. Please be sure to include your full name and email address when contacting Natural Wellness to edit your personal information. Also, please allow one (1) week for email requests and three (3) weeks for postal mail requests to be fulfilled.

**Top**

**How does Natural Wellness protect kids' privacy?**

Natural Wellness does not knowingly sell or market to, solicit information from, or sell products or services for purchases to, individuals under 18 years of age. If you are a parent or legal guardian of a child under the age of 18, and your child has provided Natural Wellness with personal information using the Natural Wellness Website, you may contact Natural Wellness using the Contact Information provided above and we will delete any and all personal information about your child as soon as reasonably possible.

**Top**

**What are cookies? How does Natural Wellness use cookies on its site?**

Some of our Web Sites will send a "cookie," a small text file, to your computer. This allows us to recognize your computer the next time you visit, without bothering you with another request to register. And, if you use an online "shopping cart," cookies allow us to keep track of the products you purchase. If you do not wish to receive cookies, please refer to the "Help" file of your Internet browser either to learn how to block all cookies or how to receive a warning before a cookie is stored. To learn more about cookies, we encourage you to visit [www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/).

If you visit the Natural Wellness Website to browse, read, or download information, we collect and store some "visitor information" from you, such as the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using, the date and time you access the Natural Wellness Website, and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to the Natural Wellness Website. We use this information to measure the traffic on the Natural Wellness Website and to help us make the Natural Wellness Website more useful. We delete this information after some time.

**Top**

**How do I know if my subscription information is secure?**

We recognize our responsibility to protect the information you entrust to us. Natural Wellness uses a variety of secure techniques to protect your information, including secure servers, firewalls, and encryption of financial data.

The Natural Wellness Website also may make chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or newsgroups available to you. Please remember that any personally identifiable information you provide in these areas is also available to other users, and you should exercise caution before deciding to disclose such data.

**Top**

**What about links to other Websites and services?**

The Natural Wellness Website may contain links to other third-party Websites. Natural Wellness does not control the privacy practices of these Websites. You should review those policies before providing any personal information. Natural Wellness is not responsible for the content or practices of any linked third party Websites, and we provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.

**Top**

**Can Natural Wellness change this privacy policy?**

Natural Wellness may change this privacy policy at any time without notice. However, if the Privacy Policy changes, we will post an updated version on the Natural Wellness Website. The policy revision date will be posted at the bottom of the page.

**Top**

Updated: April 2, 2009
